Guide to the Center for American Music Photos CAM.PHOTOS.2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Title page of "Old Folks at Home" by Foster, featuring the Swedish Ladies Quartet (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36017)
- Title page of Foster's "Old Folks at Home" published by B. Williams, London (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36018)
- Title page of Foster's "Old Folks at Home" published by The Musical Treasury, London (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36019)
- Title page of "Old Folks at Home" by Foster, featuring Christine Nilsson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36020)
- Title page of "Old Folks at Home" by Foster, featuring Adelina Patti (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36021)
- Southern Musical Bouquet edition of "Parthenia to Ingomar" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36022)
- Title page of Foster's "She Was All the World to Me" published by Horace Water, NY, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36023)
- Title page of "When Old Friends Were Here" and "She was All the World to Me" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36024)
- Title page of Foster's "Under the Willow She's Sleeping" published by Oliver Ditson, Boston, 1863 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36025)
- Title page of "American Ballad Quadrille," an arrangement of Foster songs by Thomas Baker (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36026)
- Title page of "The Dark Sett" by S. O. Dyer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36027)
- Title page to "The San Francisco Quadrilles, arranged from the most favourite Negro Melodies for the Piano Forte, Respectfully dedicated to the Ladies of California by their Sincere Admirer, George Peck" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36028)
- Title page of "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" by Foster (but Foster's name does not appear on this edition) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36029)
- Title page of Foster's "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" published by John C. Schreiner & Son, Macon, GA, 1863 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36030)
- Title page of Foster's "Ellen Bayne" arranged for guitar, published by Firth, Pond & Co., NY, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36031)
- Title page of German edition of "My Old Kentucky Home" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36032)
- Page 1 of German edition of "My Old Kentucky Home" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36033)
- Title page of tenth edition of "My Old Kentucky Home, Good Night" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36034)
- Title page of an English edition of "Old Black Joe" ("Poor Old Joe") by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36035)
- Title page of Foster's "Poor Old Joe" published by Musical Bouquet, London (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36036)
- Title page of Foster's "Old Dog Tray" published by The Musical Treasury, London (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36037)
- Title page of an English edition of "Old Dog Tray" ("My Old Dog Tray") by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36038)
- Title page of an English edition of "Old Dog Tray" by Foster, arranged by E. J. Westrop (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36039)
- Title page of Danish edition of "Old Folks at Home" ("De Gamie Derhjemme") by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36040)
- Title page of 10th edition of "Old Folks at Home" by Foster, showing E. P. Christy as composer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36041)
- Title page of Foster's "Old Folks at Home" published by Firth Pond & Co., NY, 15th edition (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36042)
- Title page of English edition of "Uncle Ned" by Foster, arranged by W. Wilson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36043)
- Title page of Foster's "Some Folks" published by Robert Cocks & Co., London (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36044)
- Title page of Australian edition of "Willie We Have Missed You" by Foster (but Foster's name is not included) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 36045)
- Foster's piano, on loan from the Carnegie Museum, in the Stephen Foster Memorial museum. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38289)
- Charles Connick's stained glass window "theatre" in the Stephen Foster Memorial lobby (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38290)
- Window "Ah! May the Red Rose Live Alway" from the Stephen Foster Museum (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38292)
- Windows representing "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" and "The Glendy Burk" in the Stephen Foster Museum, vertical (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38293.01)
- Windows representing "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" and "The Glendy Burk" in the Stephen Foster Museum, horizontal (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38293.02)
- Windows representing "Old Dog Tray" and "Nelly Bly" in the museum corridor (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38294)
- Close up of the theater window in the Stephen Foster Memorial lobby (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38295.01)
- Stained glass window and window dedicated to Lilly in the Stephen Foster Memorial lobby (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38295.02)
- Windows representing "Massa's in de cold Ground" and "Old Black Joe" in the Stephen Foster museum (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38296)
- Stained glass windows representing "Open thy Lattice Love" and "Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38297)
- Colored cartoon of the Stephen Foster window at the Temple of Memories Mausoleum at Allegheny Cemetery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38298.01)
- Close up on Stephen Foster on the stained glass window at the Temple of Memories Mausoleum at Allegheny Cemetery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38298.02)
- Stained glass windows representing "Old Folks at Home" and "My Old Kentucky Home" in the Foster museum (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38299)
- Close up on stained glass window representing Stephen Foster in the museum corridor (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38300)
- Morrison Foster as a middle-aged man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 38973)
- Portrait of Mr. Glendy Burke for whom the steamboat in Foster's song was named (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 40575)
- Enlargement of Foster daguerreotype (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 40769)
- Enlargement of Foster tintype (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 40770)
- Enlargement of bronze medal given to J. K. Lilly by the people of Pittsburgh (front only) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 43869)
- Plan of Lawrenceville in 1814, presumably made by "Father" John Taylor of Pittsburgh, corrected (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 44375)
- Bellevue Hospital, 1873 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 45056)
- Two maps of the town of Lawrenceville as laid out by William B. Foster, December 10, 1814 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 46035)
- Newspaper reproduction of "The Great Baby Show" by Foster in The Pittsburgh Post, September 26, 1856 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 46037)
- Title page of "I Will Be True to Thee" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 46038)
- Page from the Clark's School Visitor showing Foster's "The Merry, Merry Month of May" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 46040)
- Title page of Foster's "When This [sic] War is Ended" published by Horace Waters, NY, 1862 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 46043)
- Title page of "No One to Love" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 46045)
- Oversized daguerreotype of E.P. Christy and dog (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 47723)